https://iseinc.com/_shop/privacy-policy.html

Variac, General, Single Phase
Variac,
Single Phase, 120VAC Input, 0-140V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 120VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 480VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac, General Three Phase
Variac,
Three Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Three Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac,
316 Stainless Steel Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
Steel Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
23 Watts/sq in for Light Oils, Degreasing Solutions, Heat Transfer Oils
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
23 Watts/sq in for Light Oils, Degreasing Solutions, Heat Transfer Oils
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
15 Watts/sq in for Medium weight oils and heat transfer fluid
23 Watts/sq in for Light Oils, Degreasing Solutions, Heat Transfer Oils
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
23 Watts/sq in for Light Oils, Degreasing Solutions, Heat Transfer Oils
8 Watts/sq in for Heavy Oils, Fuel Oils
Incoloy Sheath Immersion Heaters
3 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
5 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
6 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
23 Watts/sq in for Forced Air and Gases - Caustic Solutions - Degreasing Solutions
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
23 Watts/sq in for Forced Air and Gases - Caustic Solutions - Degreasing Solutions
16 Watts/sq in for Medium Weight Oils - Heat Transfer Oils - Liquid Paraffin
48 Watts/sq in for Process Water
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
16 Watts/sq in for Medium Weight Oils - Heat Transfer Oils -
Liquid Paraffin
23 Watts/sq in for Forced Air and Gases - Caustic Solutions - Degreasing Solutions
48 Watts/sq in for Process Water
Copper Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
Last added items
Subtotal:
Variac, General, Single Phase
Variac,
Single Phase, 120VAC Input, 0-140V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 120VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac,
Single Phase, 480VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac, General Three Phase
Variac,
Three Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-280V Output
Variac,
Three Phase, 240VAC Input, 0-560V Output
Variac,
316 Stainless Steel Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (316 SS)
Steel Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Steel)
Incoloy Sheath Immersion Heaters
3 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
5 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
6 Inch Flange Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Incoloy)
Copper Sheath Immersion Heaters
1 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
1-1/4 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
2-1/2 Inch NPT Screw Plug Immersion Heater (Copper)
Privacy Policy
ISE PRIVACY POLICYThe Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to ISE, Inc. to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So, we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, ISE, Inc. follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone. We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users. NOTICEWe will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site make a purchase, when you download software or signup for email newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. To help you quickly find products, services or information. To help us create content most relevant to you. To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from ISE, Inc.. ACCESSWe will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the Visitor Center. There, you can:View and edit personal information you have already given us. Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information, or whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail. Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products. Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on www.iseinc.com, your information stays with you. SECURITYISE, Inc. has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. When you place orders or access your personal account information, you're utilizing secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.ISE, Inc. strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHAREWhen you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time. For your convenience, we do save billing information in case you want to order from us again..ISE, Inc. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ISE, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ISE, Inc. and its family of Websites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ISE, Inc., its Websites, or the public.
Sign up for ISE, Inc. news
Email
*
Subscribe
Can't subscribe you right now. Try later
Thank you for subscribing to the newsletter! We hope you enjoy shopping at ISE, Inc.
Contact ISE
10100 Royalton Rd., Cleveland, OH, US, 44133
(440) 237-3200
Send a message
Offers
Sale
Coming soon
New!
Info links
Search ISE
Shipping
Sitemap
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Return Policy
Cookies and Tracking
Services
Shipping info
Contact us
© 1946 - 2020 ISE, Inc.. All rights reserved.
Powered by X-Cart
ISE has been the preferred source for  Instrumentation, VARIAC® Variable Transformers, SCR Power Controllers, Electric Heating Elements, Thermocouples and Instrumentation Service to industry since 1946.
Place your order via this site or call (440) 237-3200 if you have questions, need assistance or prefer ordering via phone.  We also provide many standard and custom items not included on this site.  Click here to contact ISE
